gameserpent.com 2015-06-07

# Games GameSerpent.com

Privacy policy

This privacy policy explains how we use personal information collected at this site. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described herein. Our site is not directed to children under the age of 13. You must be 13 years of age or older to access this site. Use of this site by persons under the age of 13 is prohibited. See Below for Opt-out Information. 

**Please Note:** the privacy practices set forth in this document are for GameSerpent.com only. When viewing other sites linked to from here, please review the privacy policies posted at those other sites.

**Collection of Information**  
Use of this site is only for the use of persons above the age of 13. You must be 13 years of age or older to access this site. We do not knowingly collect any information that may personally identify children under the age of 13. We do collect personally identifiable information, like nick names, email addresses, and user submitted comments when voluntarily submitted by our users assert they are above the age of 13. Our membership registration page clearly states "NO CHILD UNDER 13 YEARS OF AGE IS ALLOWED TO CREATE, OR HAVE A MEMBERSHIP AT GAMESERPENT.COM. IF YOU ARE UNDER 13, YOU ARE NOT AUTHORIZED TO REGISTER FOR MEMBERSHIP ". 

If you are a parent or legal guardian that believes your child under 13 years of age has submitted personal information to the site, you can contact us at the e-mail address listed below (in Contact Info) or through our contact page on the site. We will promptly delete the information upon learning that it relates to a child under the age of 13. We believe that parents should supervise their children's online activities and consider using parental control tools available from online services and software manufacturers that help provide a child friendly online environment. These tools can also prevent children from otherwise disclosing their name, address and other personal information online without parental permission. 

Nick name and email information is used to login and submit high scores for games and is used to protect the security or liability of the site or to respond to law enforcement, if necessary, and do not use it for any other purpose. The name and email information you provide is only used to fulfill your specific request to access this site and is not shared with anyone unless we are legally required to do so. User submitted comments and profile bio comments are publicy viewable and searchable by robots. You should not disclose any personal information in comments here or leave them blank if you do not want it shared.

**Cookie/Tracking Technology**  
This site may use cookies and other tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookies and other tracking technology are useful for determining information such as browser type and operating system or tracking the number of visitors to the site as well as help provide an understanding of how our visitors use the site. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. We do not share cookie tracking information or any of your personal information with third parties. We do not store Cookie information. 

**Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements**  
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

**Distribution of Information**  
As previously stated, Nick name and email information is used to login and submit high scores for games and is used to protect the security or liability of the site or to respond to law enforcement, if necessary, and does not use it for any other purpose. The information you provide is only used to fulfill your specific request to access this site and is not shared with anyone unless weare legally required to do so. We may share information with governmental or law enforcement agencies. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these agencies for marketing purposes.

**Opt-out**  
If you wish you may opt-out from such information collected and used by our advertisers by visiting NAI's opt-out page at <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>. 

We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted and are not retroactive.

**Contact info**  
You may contact the owners GameSerpent by sending an email to gameserpent[ATsign]gmail.com relplace [Atsign] with @.
